Women's Bookstore collection
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Women's Bookstore collection
1937 - 2018, predominant 1937-1997
F-111
Q104891174
2.57 m of textual records 22 photographs 212 newspapers 2 sound recordings
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
PHYSICAL DESCRIPTION Fonds include 1 sound recording that is stored on 8 audio cassettes and 1 born-digital sound recording. GENERAL NOTE The 22 photographs located in are located in file F-111-4-0-0-2.
published
Full
Revised
Title based on provenance of the collection.
The Women's Bookstore collection consists of materials relating to the operation of several Vancouver women's organizations and reflects the issues that dominated the women's movement throughout the 1970s. Consistent with the community based nature of women's movements during this period, the scope and content of the collection reflects the diversity common to a phenomenon rather than the administrative and subject coherence found in records generated by a single organization. As such, the collection as whole gains its coherence due primarily to the interdependence rather than independence of the individual items to one another. This also applies to the records generated by autonomous organizations in the collection. While the different organizations should be regarded as distinct, a good deal of the records concern the communication between various organizations and women's groups across the country or identify issues of concern to a broad range of organizations. Thus, the collection as whole should be regarded as a record of a dynamic process in which a common ideology served to unify the aims of distinctive organizations, persons, and subjects.
The collection is comprised of the records of the Women's Bookstore, Women's Caucus, A Woman's Place, Transition House, the British Columbia Federation of Women and the Morris and Helen Belkin Art Gallery. Includes constitutions, minutes, reports, correspondence, position papers, and sound recordings. Also includes newsletters from women's centres across British Columbia and Canada, subject files, and an assortment of feminist publications.
The materials were arranged by the Archivist. Subject files were created from material received in considerable disorder, and runs of publications were put together from copies scattered throughout the collection.
Hudson, Kathleen; Dunn, Margo; Braid, Kate; Lancaster, Jan; Women's Bookstore; Photographic materials; Sound recordings; Textual records; Records in electronic form (digitized); Business and commerce; Women; Politics
All accessions have been processed as of September 2018. No further accruals are expected.
The Vancouver Women's Bookstore collection was stored in the basement of the Vancouver Women's Bookstore, until 1980 when Margo Dunn removed it only 10 days before an arsonist's fire destroyed the store. Ms. Dunn stored the material and made additions to the collection. Contributions were also made by Kate Braid, Jan Lancaster, and others. In 1985, Kathleen Hudson took over physical custody and donated the material to the Simon Fraser University Archives in 1996. Material in F-111-9 was donated by Alexandra Bischoff.
Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as stipulated by Archives policy or the donor. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
Series descriptions and file lists are available. An item list is available for the publications in series 8. A structure of the women's movement in Vancouver is available in the hard copy version of the finding aid maintained in the Archives Reading Room.
- Women's Bookstore records, 1971 - 1984; F-111-1; 12 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of those records relating directly to the Women's Bookstore. Includes correspondence, grant applications, in-house catalogs, and log books.
  Access to some records in this series is restricted in order to protect the personal privacy of individuals named or described in the documents. Please consult the unit list and the archivist for further details. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
  - Women's Bookstore - start-up, 1971; F-111-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 111-1)
    Textual records
    Open
  - Women's Bookstore - miscellaneous, 1971 - 1978; F-111-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 111-1)
  - Women's Bookstore - catalogues, 1973 - 1984; F-111-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 111-1)
  - Women's Bookstore - flyers, 1973 - 1980; F-111-1-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 111-1)
  - Women's Bookstore - Log Book, 1972 - 1973; F-111-1-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 111-1)
    Restricted in whole
  - Women's Bookstore - Log Book, 1973 - 1974; F-111-1-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 111-1)
  - Women's Bookstore - Log Book, 1974; F-111-1-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 111-1)
  - Women's Bookstore - Log Book, 1974 - 1975; F-111-1-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 111-1)
  - Women's Bookstore - Log Book, 1975 - 1976; F-111-1-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 111-1)
  - Women's Bookstore - Log Book, 1976 - 1978; F-111-1-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 111-1)
  - Women's Bookstore - Log Book, 1978 - 1983; F-111-1-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 111-1)
- Women's Caucus records, 1969 - 1971; F-111-2; 8 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records of the Vancouver Women's Caucus. The group began as the Women's Caucus at Simon Fraser University. In 1969 the group moved off-campus in order to reach a larger number of women. The activities of the caucus included demonstrations, discussions, and abortion counseling. It also dealt with issues such as jobs, education, and society's responsibility for children. In 1969 it founded the feminist newspaper, The Pedestal (later known as Women Can), and in 1970 it organized the Abortion Cavalcade/Caravan to Ottawa. Includes correspondence, minutes, articles and position papers.
  Vancouver Women's Caucus
  Access to some records in this series is restricted in order to protect the personal privacy of individuals named or described in the documents. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
  - Women's Caucus - History, 1970; F-111-2-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 111-2)
  - Women's Caucus - Minutes, 1969 - 1970; F-111-2-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 111-2)
  - Women's Caucus - Correspondence -- B.C. Interior, 1969 - 1971; F-111-2-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 111-2)
    Restricted in part
  - Women's Caucus - Correspondence -- Alberta, 1970; F-111-2-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 111-2)
  - Women's Caucus - Correspondence -- Ontario, 1970; F-111-2-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 111-2)
  - Women's Caucus - Correspondence -- Toronto, 1970 - 1971; F-111-2-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 111-2)
  - Women's Caucus - Correspondence -- re Pedestal, 1970 - 1971; F-111-2-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 111-2)
  - Women's Caucus - Correspondence -- miscellaneous, 1969 - 1970; F-111-2-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 111-2)
  - Women's Caucus - Abortion Cavalcade / Abortion Caravan, 1970; F-111-2-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 111-2)
  - Women's Caucus - Papers, 1970; F-111-2-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 111-2)
- A Woman's Place records, 1972 - 1973; F-111-3; 8 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records of A Woman's Place Society, formed to establish and operate a house for women in Vancouver. The house was to provide a centre where women could meet to discuss issues and common problems, and to act together. The house would also serve as the focus for the development of several projects relating to childcare, health, information resources and legal aid. Includes constitution, correspondence, proposals, reports, logbooks, and newsletters.
  A Woman's Place Society
  Access to some records in this series is restricted in order to protect the personal privacy of individuals named or described in the documents. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
  - A Woman's Place - history / minutes, 1972; F-111-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 111-2)
  - A Woman's Place - proposals / reports, 1972; F-111-3-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 111-2)
  - A Woman's Place - application for "A Woman's Place", 1972 - 1973; F-111-3-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 111-2)
  - A Woman's Place - Constitution / History, 1972 - 1973; F-111-3-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 111-2)
  - A Woman's Place - Log Books, 1972 - 1973; F-111-3-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
  - A Woman's Place - Correspondence, 1973; F-111-3-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
  - A Woman's Place - Newsletter, 1972; F-111-3-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
  - A Woman's Place - Health Group, 1972; F-111-3-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
  - A Woman's Place - Library, 1972; F-111-3-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
  - A Woman's Place - Address cards, [ca 1972] - [ca 1973]; F-111-3-0-0-10 (Archival box - small 111-35)
    Pending review
- Transition House records, 1977 - 1985; F-111-4; 13 cm of textual records 22 photographs; Physical description: the 22 photographs are located in file F-111-4-0-0-2
  Series consists of records relating to the Vancouver Transition House, and other transition houses in British Columbia. Transition houses were set up to offer a refuge for women and children forced to leave their homes due to violent and abusive situations. The goal of the transition houses was to secure the safety and health of the women and children in their care, and to ensure that they not return to unresolved and dangerous situations. Includes academic papers, articles, briefs, correspondence, minutes and publications.
  Vancouver Transition House
  Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as stipulated by Archives policy or the donor. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
  - Transition House - papers, 1977; F-111-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
  - Vancouver Transition House - miscellaneous, 1977 - 1980; F-111-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
    Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Vancouver Transition House - articles and reports, 1977 - 1984; F-111-4-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
  - Vancouver Transition House - Women's Research Centre project, 1979; F-111-4-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
  - Vancouver Transition House - United Way Committee on Support, 1979 - 1980; F-111-4-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
  - Vancouver Transition House - Statistics -- accomodated / refused, 1979 - 1983; F-111-4-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
  - Vancouver Transition House - review of Monroe House, 1980; F-111-4-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
  - Vancouver Transition House - newspaper clippings re 1982 move, F-111-4-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
  - Vancouver Transition House - support letters, 1983 - 1984; F-111-4-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
  - Vancouver Transition House - press releases, 1983 - 1985; F-111-4-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
  - Vancouver Transition House - strategic plan, 1984; F-111-4-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
  - Vancouver Transition House - Society minutes, 1985; F-111-4-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
  - Vancouver Transition House - YWCA correspondence, 1985; F-111-4-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 111-3)
  - Vancouver Transition House - support letters, 1985; F-111-4-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 111-4)
  - Vancouver Transition House - newspaper clippings re closure, 1985; F-111-4-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 111-4)
  - Vernon Transition House, 1978; F-111-4-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 111-4)
  - Transition House - publications, 1982 - 1984; F-111-4-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 111-4)
- British Columbia Federation of Women records, 1974 - 1982; F-111-5; Analog originals: 8 cm of textual records 1 sound recording (8 audiocassettes) Digitized materials: Preservation copies - 15 wav files (14.11 GB) Access copies - 15 mp3 files (617.3 MB)
  Series consists of records of the British Columbia Federation of Women. The BCFW was an umbrella organization for women's groups in BC; its objective was to bring about women's liberation through fundamental social change. Includes reports from various sub-committees of the BCFW, such as the BC Association of Non-Status Women, Rights of Women in Prison, Rights of Lesbians, and others. Also includes the BCFW constitution, correspondence, newspapers, agendas, standing committee reports, newsletters, handbooks and an audio recording (on 8 audio cassettes) of a BCFW Standing Committee meeting in October 197[5].
  British Columbia Federation of Women
  Analog originals were digitized by the Archives in October 2018. Digitial copies are available in mp3 (access format) and wav (preservation format) for all sound recordings in this series. Please contact the reference archivist to request copies.
  - British Columbia Federation of Women - newspaper, 1974 - 1975; F-111-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 111-4)
  - British Columbia Federation of Women - Subcommittee reports, 1974 - 1976; F-111-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 111-4)
  - British Columbia Federation of Women - correspondence recieved, 1974 - 1976; F-111-5-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 111-4)
  - British Columbia Federation of Women - committees, agendas, etc., 1974 - 1982; F-111-5-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 111-4)
  - British Columbia Federation of Women - Standing Committee, 1975 - 1976; F-111-5-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 111-4)
    - BCFW Standing Committee Meeting, October 1974 - October 1979; F-111-5-0-0-5-1; 8 audio cassettes 15 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-3248, Audio cassette OBJ-3249, Audio cassette OBJ-3250, Audio cassette OBJ-3251, Audio cassette OBJ-3252, Audio cassette OBJ-3253, Audio cassette OBJ-3254, Audio cassette OBJ-3255)
      Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      OBJ-3254 is damaged; only Side A of cassette was captured.
      .wav files also available in .mp3 format.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-111-5-0-1.1 (orig), C-111-5-0-2.1 (orig), C-111-5-0-3.1 (orig), C-111-5-0-4.1 (orig), C-111-5-0-5.1 (orig), C-111-5-0-6.1 (orig), C-111-5-0-7.1 (orig), C-111-5-0-8.1 (orig), F-111-item1, F-111-item3, F-111-item5, F-111-item7, F-111-item9, F-111-item11, F-111-item13, F-111-item15.
      - OBJ-3248_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3248_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3249_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3249_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3250_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3250_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3251_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3251_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3252_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3252_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3253_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3253_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3254_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3255_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3255_SideB.wav
  - British Columbia Federation of Women - newsletters and handbooks, 1975 - 1980; F-111-5-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 111-4)
  - British Columbia Federation of Women - Constitution, 1977 - 1982; F-111-5-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 111-4)
  - British Columbia Federation of Women - Action for Women Conference, [ca 1974] - [ca 1979]; F-111-5-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 111-4)
- Women's Centres - Newsletters, 1970 - 1982; F-111-6; 12 cm of textual records
  Series consists of newsletters from various women's centres across Canada. Although diverse in scope, women's centres are similar in that they exist to provide services specifically for women. Included are newsletters from British Columbia women's centres in Aldergrove, North Vancouver, Port Coquitlam, Prince George, Richmond, Surrey, SFU, Vancouver, and Victoria. Includes newsletters from centres in Alberta, Ontario, New Brunswick, Saskatchewan, and the Yukon.
  - BC Women's Centres - Aldergrove -- Ishtar, 1974; F-111-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - BC Women's Centres - Nanaimo, [ca 1974] - [ca 1979]; F-111-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - BC Women's Centres - North Shore, 1974 - 1981; F-111-6-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - BC Women's Centres - Port Coquitlam, 1976 - 1980; F-111-6-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - BC Women's Centres - Prince George-- Aspen: A Newsletter for and by Northern Women, 1979 - 1981; F-111-6-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - BC Women's Centres - Richmond, 1979; F-111-6-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - BC Women's Centres - South Surrey / White Rock -- Woman's Place Association, 1981 - 1982; F-111-6-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - BC Women's Centres - SFU, 1975 - 1976; F-111-6-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - BC Women's Centres - Vancouver, [ca 1974] - [ca 1979]; F-111-6-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - BC Women's Centres - Victoria, 1974; F-111-6-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - Alberta Women's Centres - Calgary YWCA Women's Centre, 1974; F-111-6-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - Alberta Women's Centres - Edmonton, 1975; F-111-6-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - New Brunswick Women's Centres - St. John's, [ca 1970] - [ca 1979]; F-111-6-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - Ontario Women's Centres - Guelph -- Virago, 1974; F-111-6-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - Ontario Women's Centres - Kingston, 1976; F-111-6-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - Ontario Women's Centres - Kitchener / Waterloo - "Women's Place", 1974 - 1975; F-111-6-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - Ontario Women's Centres - Ottawa, 1974; F-111-6-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - Ontario Women's Centres - "The Woman's Place", 1974 - 1976; F-111-6-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - Ontario Women's Centres - Women's Information Centre, 1975; F-111-6-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - Saskatchewan Women's Centres - Saskatoon, 1974 - 1975; F-111-6-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - Yukon Women's Centres - Whitehorse -- Victoria Faulkner Women's Centre, 1975; F-111-6-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
  - Women's Centres - miscellaneous, 1975; F-111-6-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 111-5)
- Subject files, 1937 - 1990; F-111-7; 1.94 m of textual records; Predominant dates: 1965-1985.
  Series consists of files relating to a number of issues, activities, and areas of interest to the women's movement in North America. Files contain material on such diverse topics as birth control, socialism, pornography, rape and beauty pageants. Also includes files on organizations, groups, and movements in the fight for women's rights, such as the Younger Lesbian Association, Women Against the Budget, Vancouver Rape Relief, Concerned Citizens for Choice on Abortion, the Childcare Occupation Forces, and others. Includes articles, clippings, newsletters, academic papers, reports, posters, calendars, and ephemera.
  Series was arranged by the archivist into two sub-series, one for general files, the other for files on particular organizations.
  - General, 1937 - 1990; F-111-7-1; 1.37 m of textual records
    Sub-series consists of reference files relating general subjects.
    Files are arranged alphabetically.
    - Abortion, 1962 - 1980; F-111-7-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 111-6)
    - Academic Discrimination, 1968 - 1976; F-111-7-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 111-6)
    - Advertising, 1969 - 1977; F-111-7-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 111-6)
    - Arts 1/2, 1971 - 1982; F-111-7-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 111-6)
    - Arts 2/2, 1971 - 1982; F-111-7-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 111-6)
    - Arts - film, 1970 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 111-7)
    - Arts - music and songs, 1971 - 1980; F-111-7-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 111-7)
    - Arts - poetry, 1972 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 111-7)
    - Battered Women / Violence Against Women 1/2, 1976 - 1984; F-111-7-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 111-7)
    - Battered Women / Violence Against Women 2/2, 1976 - 1984; F-111-7-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 111-7)
    - Beauty pageants, 1969; F-111-7-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 111-8)
    - Bibliographies - books and authors, 1966 - 1980; F-111-7-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 111-8)
    - Birth Control, 1937 - 1983; F-111-7-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 111-8)
    - The Bitch Manifesto, F-111-7-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 111-8)
    - Book catalogues 1/2, 1969 - 1976; F-111-7-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 111-8)
    - Book catalogues 2/2, 1969 - 1976; F-111-7-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 111-8)
    - British Columbia, 1972 - 1984; F-111-7-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 111-8)
    - Brown, Rosemary, 1978 - 1984; F-111-7-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 111-8)
    - Calendars, 1973 - 1976; F-111-7-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 111-8)
    - Calendars, 1976 - 1983; F-111-7-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 111-9)
    - Canada, [ca 1970] - [ca 1979]; F-111-7-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 111-9)
    - Childcare/Daycare, 1970 - 1978; F-111-7-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 111-9)
    - Childcare/Daycare, 1973 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 111-9)
    - Childcare/Daycare - Newsletters, 1974 - 1979; F-111-7-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 111-9)
    - Directories, Guides and Resources - British Columbia, 1974 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 111-9)
    - Directories, Guides and Resources - Canada, 1979 - 1982; F-111-7-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 111-10)
    - Feminist Calendars, 1973 - 1977; F-111-7-1-0-27
    - Event Posters / Press Releases 1/2, 1970 - 1982; F-111-7-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 111-10)
    - Event Posters / Press Releases 2/2, 1970 - 1982; F-111-7-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 111-10)
    - Health 1/2, 1965 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 111-10)
    - Health 2/2, 1965 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 111-10)
    - Health, 1979; F-111-7-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 111-10)
    - Health - Genital, 1971 - 1981; F-111-7-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 111-11)
    - Homosexuality 1/2, 1967 - 1982; F-111-7-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 111-11)
    - Homosexuality 2/2, 1967 - 1982; F-111-7-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 111-11)
    - Indochinese Women - Conference, 1970 - 1971; F-111-7-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 111-11)
      Vancouver Indochinese Women's Conference; Textual records
    - Language, F-111-7-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 111-11)
    - Law 1/2, 1970 - 1982; F-111-7-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 111-11)
    - Law 2/2, 1970 - 1982; F-111-7-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 111-11)
    - Law - Vancouver People's Law School, 1971 - 1984; F-111-7-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 111-11)
      Vancouver People's Law School; Textual records
    - Lesbians, 1970 - 1983; F-111-7-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 111-11)
    - Lesbians - Conference, 1981; F-111-7-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 111-12)
    - Lesbians - Journals, Newsletters, 1973 - 1982; F-111-7-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 111-12)
    - Makara - note cards and ephemera, 1976 - 1977; F-111-7-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 111-12)
      Makara Magazine; Textual records
    - Marriage and Divorce, 1969 - 1974; F-111-7-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 111-12)